{
    "title": "Super Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "questionText": "Which of the following countries is NOT a province of the Northwest Argentina?",
            "choices": ["Jujuy", "Salta", "Misiones", "Tucuman"],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which mountain range borders the region?",
            "choices": ["Atlas", "Rockies", "Alps", "Andes"],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of the following is the name of an independent country?",
            "choices": ["Albania", "Alberta", "America", "Athabaska"],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionText": "How is classified the climate in the region?",
            "choices": ["Polar", "Subtropical", "Temperate", "Arid"],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of theses Battles hapenned in the region?",
            "choices": [
                "Platine War",
                "Jordanist Rebellion",
                "Battle of Salta",
                "Falklands War",
                "Conquest of the Chaco"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which language is spoken in Norwest Argentina?",
            "choices": ["Spanish", "French", "Portuguese", "English"],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which color does not appear in the Argentinian flag?",
            "choices": ["Blue", "Yellow", "Red", "White"],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of these countries borders the region?",
            "choices": ["Chile", "Uruguay", "Venezuela", "Peru"],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of the following provinces is the smallest?",
            "choices": [
                "Catamarca",
                "Salta",
                "Jujuy",
                "Tucuman"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionText": "What's is the name of the salt desert in Jujuy?",
            "choices": ["Salar de Uyuni", "Salinas Grandes", "Salar Grande", "Salina de Jujuy", "Salina Magna"],
            "answer": 1
        }
        
        
    ]
}
